Finding aid for the Hearst Corporation Los Angeles Examiner photographs, negatives and clippings - oversize portrait and subject files 7000.3
USC Libraries Special Collections
- Oversize Portrait Files
  - C
    - Coogan, Jackie -- Actor (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Cook, Cooke, A-Z (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Cooley, A-Z (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Cooper, A-Z (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Cooper, Gary -- Actor (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Cooper, Jackie -- Actor (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Coplon, Judith (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Cora-Corh (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Corday, Mara -- Actress (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Corey, Wendell -- Mr. and Mrs. -- Alice Wiley (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Cori-Corl (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Corm-Corq (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Cornell, Katherine -- Actress (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Corr-Cors (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Cort-Corz (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Cos-Cot (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Costello, A-Z (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Costello, Frank -- Gambler (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Costello, Lou -- Actor -- And wife (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Cotten, Joseph -- Actor (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Cotten, Leo -- Drawings by the Examiner Artist (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Cou (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Cov-Coz (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Cowan-Cowen (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Cox, A-Z (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Cra-Craz (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Craig -- Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Craig, James (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Crain, Jeanne -- Actress (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Crain, Jeanne -- With Husband Paul Brinkman (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Crane -- Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Crawford, A-Z (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Crawford, Broderick (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Crawford, Joan -- Actress (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Cre-Crk (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Cripps, Stafford, Sir (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Croa-Crol (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Crom-Crov (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Cronin, A-Z (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Crosby, A-Z (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Crosby, Bing (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Cross, A-Z (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Crow-Croz (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Crowley, A-Z (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Crp-Crz (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Cu-Cz (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Cugat, Xavier -- And Wife (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Cummings, Robert -- Actor (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Cummins, A-Z (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Cunningham, A-Z (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Curran, Joseph -- Union Leader (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Curry, A-Z (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Curtis -- Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Curtis, Alan -- Actor (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Curtis, Anthony -- Mr. and Mrs. -- Janet Leigh (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - D
    - D'Aquino, Iva Toguri (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Daa-Dak (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Dahl, Arlene -- Actress (Box 36, Folder 12 - 14)
    - Dailey, Dan Jr. -- Actor (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Dal (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Dall -- Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Dallinger, Nat (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Dalton, Dorothy -- Actress (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Dam-Dar (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Damita, Lila (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Damone, Vic -- Singer (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Dane, Patricia -- Actress (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Daniels -- Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Dantine -- Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Daq-Dar (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Darcel, Denise (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Darin, Bobby -- Singer (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Darnell, Linda (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Das-Dat (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Dav (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Davey, Chuck -- Boxer (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Davidson -- Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Davies -- Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Davis, A-D (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Bette -- Actress (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Davis, E-I (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Davis, Glenn -- Los Angeles Rams Back (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Davis, J-O (Box 38, Folder 3 - 7)
    - Davis, Joan -- Comedian (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Davis, P-Z (Box 38, Folder 8 - 10)
    - Daw-Daz (Box 36, Folder 9 - 11)
    - Daw, Marjorie -- Actress (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Dawe, Dawes, A-Z (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Day, Doris (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Day, Laraine -- Actress (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - De Carlo, Yvonne (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - De Cordova, Arturo -- Actor (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - De Gasperi, Alcide (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - De Gaulle, Charles, General (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - De Havilland, Olivia -- Actress (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - De Marigny, Nancy Oakes (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - De Shazer, Jacob (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - De Wood, Lorraine (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Dea-Deb (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Dean -- Miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Dean, Priscilla -- Actress (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Dec-Ded (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Dee-Deg (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - DeFore, Don -- Actor (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Degnan, Susan -- Kidnap, Murder Victim (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Deh-Dek (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - DeHaven, Gloria -- Actress (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Del Rio, Dolores -- Actress (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Dela-Dell (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Delm-Delz (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Dem (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - DeMaret -- Miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - DeMille -- Miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - DeMille, Cecil B. (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Dempsey, Jack (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Den (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Denfield, Louis -- Admiral (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Denmark, Royalty (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Denning, Richard (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Dennis, A-Z (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Dennis, Eugene (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Denny, and Denney -- Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Deo-Dep (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - DePaola, Peter -- Racer (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Der (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Derek, John -- Actor (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Derr, Doris -- Mrs. -- Thief (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Des (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Det-Deu (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Dev (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Dever, Paul A. -- Gov. of Mass. (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Devereux, James -- Lieutenant Colonel (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - DeVine -- Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Devore -- Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Dew-Dh (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Dewey -- Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Dewey, Thomas E. -- Large Groups (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Dewey, Thomas E. -- With Family (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Dewey, Thos. E. -- Alone (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Dewey, Thos. E. -- Small Groups (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Dia-Diz (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Dickey -- Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Didrikson, Babe -- Sportswoman (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Dietrich, Marlene (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - DiMaggio -- Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - DiMaggio, Joe -- Baseball (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Dimitrov -- Miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Dionne Quintuplets (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - DiSalle, Michael V. -- Price Administrator (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Disney -- Miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Divine, Father (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Dix, Richard -- Actor (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Dixon, A-Z (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Do-Dom (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Doby -- Miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Dodds -- Miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Domergue, Faith -- Actress (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Don-Donz (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Donaldson -- Miscellaneous (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Donlevy, Brian -- Actor (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Donnelly -- Miscellaneous (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Donovan (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Doo-Doz (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Doolittle, James (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Doolittle, James -- General and Mrs. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Douglas -- Miscellaneous (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Douglas, Kirk (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Douglas, Lewis (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Douglas, Melvin -- And Wife (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Douglas, Paul -- Mr. and Mrs. (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Douglas, Sharman (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Douglas, Wm. O. (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Dowling, Constance -- Actress (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Downey -- Miscellaneous (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Downs -- Miscellaneous (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Downs, Cathy -- Actress (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Doyle -- Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Dozier, William (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Dra-Dt (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Dragonette, Jessica (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Drake -- Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Drake, Tom -- Actor (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Draper -- Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Draves, Vicki -- Swimmer and Diver (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Drew -- Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Drew, Ellen -- Actress (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Driscoll -- Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Drobny -- Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Dropo -- Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Dru, Joanne (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Drury -- Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Dua-Dub (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Duc-Dud (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Due-Dul (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Duff -- Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Duff, Howard (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Duff, James (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Duke -- Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Dulles, John Foster (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Dulles, John Foster -- Secretary of State (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Dum (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Dun-Duq (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Duncan -- Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Duncan Sisters -- Rosetta and Vivian (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Duncan, Elizabeth (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Duncan, Frank -- Son of Elizabeth (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Dunn -- Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Dunne, Irene -- Actress (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - DuPont -- Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Dur (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Durant -- Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Durant, Jack W. -- And Wife -- Jewel Robbery Suspects (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Durante, Jimmy (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Durbin, Deanna -- Alone (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Durbin, Deanna -- Groups (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Durocher, Leo -- Baseball (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Duryea, Dan (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Dus-Duz (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Dutra, Enrico Gaspar (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Dv-Dz (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Dvorak, Ann -- Actress (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Dyer -- Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - E
    - Eaa-Ear (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Earl-Earle -- Miscellaneous (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Eas-Eaz (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Eaton, A-Z (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Eb (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Ec (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Ed (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Edison -- Miscellaneous (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Edwards -- Miscellaneous (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Ee-Ef (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Eg-Ek (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Egan, Richard -- Actor (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Egypt -- King Farouk (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Egypt, Royalty (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Eilers, Sally (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Einstein, Albert (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Eisenhower -- Miscellaneous (Box 49, Folder 12-13)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight -- 1957 Inauguration (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight -- California Visit (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight -- In Los Angeles October 1958 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight -- Korea Visit and Trip Home (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight -- Mrs. -- Mamie (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight -- Palm Springs Visit, February 1954 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight -- Press Conferences (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. -- Alone, January 1953 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. -- Family (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. -- General (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. -- General and Mrs. (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. -- Inauguration, January 1953 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight, General -- Alone -- 1944 to 1946 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight, General -- Alone -- 1947 to 1950 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight, General -- Large groups -- Up to 1950 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight, General -- Small groups -- Up to 1950 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight, President -- 1960 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight, President -- European Tour (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight, President -- Far East Tour -- Includes Tour in Alaska, Honolulu, Philippines, Formosa, Korea, Japan, etc. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight, President -- Groups, Large -- January 1953 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight, President -- Groups, Small -- January 1953 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight, President -- South American Tour (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight, President -- Special Series (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Eisenhower, General -- Biography Pictures (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Eisenhower, General -- Large Groups, 1944-1945 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Eisenhower, General -- Small Groups, 1944-1945 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Eisenhower, General -- Small Groups, 1946 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Eisenhower, General -- Small Groups, 1947 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Eisler, Gerhardt and Hans (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Ekberg, Anita (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Ela-Elg (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Elg, Taina -- Actress (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Elh-Eli (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Elj-Elk (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Ell (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Elliott -- Miscellaneous (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Ellis -- Miscellaneous (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Elm-Elz (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Ema-Eml (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Emerson, Faye (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Emm-Emz (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Ena-Enm (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Engel, Sigmund Z. (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - England -- Dowager Queen Mary -- Died March 14, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - England -- Duke of Edinburgh (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - England -- King George VI and Family (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - England -- Prince Andrew, Third Child of Queen Elizabeth (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - England -- Princess Anne (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - England -- Princess Elizabeth -- Wedding Pictures With Her and/or Philip (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - England -- Princess Elizabeth -- Wedding Pictures Without Her (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - England -- Princess Elizabeth, Canada Trip Only (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - England -- Princess Elizabeth's Baby -- Prince Charles of Edinburgh (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - England -- Princess Margaret (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - England -- Queen Elizabeth II (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - England -- Queen Elizabeth II -- Before She Became Queen -- Alone (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - England -- Queen Elizabeth II -- Before She Became Queen -- Groups With the Royal Family (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - England -- Queen Elizabeth II -- Before She Became Queen -- Miscellaneous Groups (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - England -- Queen Elizabeth II -- Before She Became Queen -- With Husband and Family (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - England -- Queen Elizabeth II -- Coronation Pictures With and Without Her (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - England -- Queen Elizabeth II -- Pictures without her (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - England -- Queen Elizabeth II and Andrew (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - England -- Queen Elizabeth II With Husband, Children, Mother, Sister (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - England -- Queen Mother Elizabeth (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - England -- Royalty, Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Enn-Eo (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Ep-Eq (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Era-Erl (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Erickson, Ericksen -- Miscellaneous (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Erm-Erz (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Erskine, Marily (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Erwin, Stuart -- Actor (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Es (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Esmond, Jill -- Actress (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Et-Ev (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Evans -- Miscellaneous (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Evans, Joan (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Evans, Madge -- Actress (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Evans, Vickie (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Everett, A-Z (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Ew-Ez (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Ewing, A-Z (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Eythe, William -- Actor (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - F
    - Fa-Faq (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas, Jr. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas, Sr. (Box 57, Folder 1a)
    - Fairless, Benjamin (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Falkenberg -- Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Falkenberg, Jinx (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Famechon, Ray (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Far (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Faris, Barry (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Farley -- Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Farmer -- Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Farrell -- Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Farrington -- Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Fas-Fd (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Fay-Faye -- Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Faye, Alice (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Faye, Julia (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Fears -- Miscellaneous (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Fek-Fep (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Feland, Leah -- 1953 Tournament of Roses Queen (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Feldman -- Miscellaneous (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Feller, Bob (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Fer-Fez (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Ferentz, Mike -- Golfer (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Ferguson -- Miscellaneous (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Fernandez, Raymond (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Ferrer, Jose (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Ferrer, Mel (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Ferreri, Elizabeth (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Fi-Fk (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Field, Betty (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Field, Fields -- Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Field, Virginia (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Fields, Benjamin (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Fields, Gracie (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Finch, Bernard, Dr. (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Finletter, Thomas K. (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Finn, Charles and George (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Firestone -- Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Fiscus, Kathy (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Fisher, Eddie (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Fisher, Fischer -- Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Fitzgerald -- Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Fitzpatrick -- Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Fla-Flh -- See Flanagan, Flanders, Fleming, Fletcher (Box 57, Folder 14 - 17)
    - Flam, Herbert -- Tennis (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Flanagan -- Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Flanders -- Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Fleming -- Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Fleming, Rhonda -- Husnard, Dr. Lewis Morrill -- Them alone (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Fletcher -- Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Fli-Fn (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Floyd -- Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Flynn -- Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Flynn, Errol (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Fo- -- See Foley, Ford, Foster, Fowler, Fox (Box 57, Folder 19 - 24)
    - Foch, Nina (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Foley -- Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Folsom, James -- Governor (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Fonda, Henry (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Fontaine -- Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Fontaine, Joan (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Forbes, Ralph (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Ford -- Miscellaneous (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Ford, Glenn -- Actor (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Ford, Henry -- And Widow (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Ford, Henry II (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Forrest, Sally (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Forrestal, James V. -- Secretary of the Navy (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Foster -- Miscellaneous (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Fowler -- Miscellaneous (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Fox -- Miscellaneous (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Fra-Frd (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - France, Shirley May (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Francis -- Miscellaneous (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Franco, Carmencita (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Franco, Francisco (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Frank -- Miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Franklin -- Miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Franks, Sir Oliver (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Franz -- Miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Fraser -- Miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Frazier -- Miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Frazier, Brenda (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Fre-Frh (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Fredericks, Pauline (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Freeman -- Miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Freeman, Joseph F. (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Freeman, Mona (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Fri-Frn (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Friedman -- Miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Friganza, Trixie (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Fro-Ftz (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Froman, Jane (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Frost -- Miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Fry-Frye -- Miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Fu-Fz (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Fuchs, Jim (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Fullmer, Gene -- Boxer (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Fulton -- Miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Furgol, Marty (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - G
    - Ga-Gak -- See Gage (Box 63, Folder 1 - 5)
    - Gable, Clark (Box 63, Folder 6 - 11)
    - Gabor, Jolie, Eva, Magda, and Sari (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Gabor, Zsa Zsa (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Gabrielson, Guy (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Gaekwar, Princess and Prince of (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Gage -- Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Gahagan, Helen -- Actress (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Gal-Gaq -- see Gale, Gallagher (Box 63, Folder 12 - 16)
    - Gale -- Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Gallagher -- Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Gallian, Ketti -- Actress (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Gandhi, Mohandas K. (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Gar-Gd --See Garcia, Gardner, Garfield, Garrett, Gates, Gay (Box 63, Folder 17 -)
    - Garbo, Greta -- Actress (Box 64, Folder 9 - 10)
    - Garcia -- Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Garden, Mary (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Gardiner, Reginald -- Actor (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Gardner -- Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Gardner, Ava (Box 64, Folder 15 - 18)
    - Garfield -- Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Garfield, John (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Garland, Judy (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Garland, Judy -- Groups (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Garland, Judy -- With Sid Luft, Daughter (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Garland, Judy -- With Vincent Minnelli (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Garner -- Miscellaneous (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Garner, Peggy Ann (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Garrett -- Miscellaneous (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Garson, Greer -- Actress (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Garsson, Henry M. -- And Brother (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Gates -- Miscellaneous (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Gavilan, Kid (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Gay -- Miscellaneous (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Gaynor, Janet -- Actress (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Gaynor, Mitzi -- Actress (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Ge-Gh (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Gehrmann, Don (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - George -- Miscellaneous (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Germany -- Royalty, Miscellaneous (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Gest, Inna -- Actress (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Gi-Gk (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Giannini -- Miscellaneous (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Gibbon, Gibbons -- Miscellaneous (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Gibbs -- Miscellaneous (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Gibson -- Miscellaneous (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Gieseking, Walter (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Gifford, Frances -- Actress (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Gilbert -- Miscellaneous (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Gilbert, Joanne (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Gillars, Mildred E. (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Gillespie -- Miscellaneous (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Gillette -- Miscellaneous (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Gish, Lillian -- Actress (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Gl (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Glab, Hazel (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Glatman, Harvey -- Slayer (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Gleason -- Miscellaneous (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Gleason, James (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Glennon, John -- Cardinal (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Glisson, Gordon -- And John (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Glucoft, Linda Joyce (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Gm-Goo (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Goddard, Paulette (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Godfrey -- Miscellaneous (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Goering, Herman -- And Fran (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Gold (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Gold -- Miscellaneous (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Gold, Harry (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Goldstein, Richard (Box 68, Folder 14)